http://womenshealthboise.com/privacy-policy/

Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purpose for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about or policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
Within this site are links to websites published elsewhere as well as our own, internal documents. Inclusions of external links are for informational purposes only. www.womenshealthboise.com or Women’s Health Associates has created and maintains this website as a patient education service.  Nothing on this website should be considered medical advice, which can only be given to you by your personal health care provider. Neither womenshealthboise.com or Women’s Health Associates makes any warranties or guarantees concerning the accuracy of the content on this website.
Terms of Use | Privacy Policy | Providers | Our Services | Patient Forms | Careers | Contact
Notice of Nondiscrimination | English | Spanish | Chínese | Serbo-Croatian | Korean | Nepali | Vietnamese | Arabic | German | Tagalog | Russian | French | Japanese | Romanian | Bantu | Persian (Farsi)
